(Raj:)Run, run, run. Don't look back.
(Leonard:)I thought we had something special.
(Raj(locks door):)So you say you can't pay your rent?
(Penny:)-Oh, Leonard?
-Hey.
(Penny:)I found these in the dryer.
(Penny:)I'm assuming they belong to Sheldon.
(Leonard:)Thanks. It's really hard
to find these in his size.
(Leonard:)So listen.
(Leonard:)I've been meaning to talk to you
about the other morning.
PENNY:
You mean you and Dr. Slutbunny?
(Leonard:)Yeah, I wanted to explain.
No. You don't owe me an explanation.
(Leonard:)-I don't?
-No, you don't.
(Leonard:)So you're not judging me?
PENNY: Oh, I'm judging you
nine ways to Sunday...
(Penny:)...but you don't owe me
an explanation.
(Leonard:)Nevertheless, I'd like to get one
on the record...
(Leonard:)...so you can understand
why I did what I did.
(Penny:)I'm listening.
(Leonard:)She let me.